https://avalanche.state.co.us/privacy-policy/

Google PlusFacebookTwitterTerms of Use
The information contained in this website is provided by the Colorado Avalanche Information Center (CAIC) as a service to the public. Some services provided require the payment of fees, and some services are free. The mission of CAIC is to provide quick access to the public of the information maintained by the office.
Use of the information to which access is provided by this website is the responsibility of the user. CAIC retains no liability for the misuse, intended or unintended, of the information obtained from this website.
This website is intended for use by natural persons in obtaining information provided by the CAIC.  Use of computerized “robots” or “data mining” of the information and images presented here is prohibited. Misuse of this website is prohibited and may result in the revocation of access to those persons or organizations using this site in a way not intended by the CAIC.
We make every effort to provide this service as efficiently and reliably as possible.  However, occasional interruptions of service do occur as we perform routine and non-routine maintenance of the machines and information provided on this website.
CAIC appreciates feedback on the subject areas covered by this website, and also accepts suggestions for improvement.  Please contact us as noted in other areas of the website of your area of concern or comment.
Collection and use of personally identifiable information
“Personal Information” is information about a natural person that is readily identifiable to that specific individual. Personal information includes such things as an individual’s name, address, phone number, or email address.
We collect no personal information about you unless you voluntarily participate in an activity that asks for information, such as submitting an observation or contacting us through the website. If you choose not to participate in these activities, your choice will not affect your ability to use other features of our web site
If personal information is requested on the web site or volunteered by the user, state and federal law may protect it. However, this information is a public record once you provide it, and may be subject to public inspection and copying if not protected by federal or state law.
Furthermore, the information contained in many kinds of documents filed with the Colorado Avalanche Information Center (CAIC) is electronically stored and may be made accessible to the public. Information maintained by CAIC is subject to the requirements of the Colorado Open Records Act.
We may collect some information about your visit to our web site. This information may include:
The Internet Protocol Address and domain name used but not the email address. The Internet Protocol Address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your Internet Service Provider or directly to your computer. We use the Internet Protocol Address to direct Internet traffic to you.
The type of browser you used.
The date and time that you visited this site.
The web pages or services you accessed at this site.
Use of User Created Content
“User Created Content” is any form of content created by any person, and includes any information, documentation, multi-media content such as videos, photographs, podcasts, graphics, digital images, audio files or other forms of media.
You must own all intellectual property in your original content that you contribute to CAIC. You must not submit or contribute any content to CAIC not originally created by you or any content which is not properly licensed to you by someone else for submission or contribution.
By submitting any User Created Content to this site or CAIC, you automatically grant to CAIC an irrevocable and perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, fully paid worldwide license, by ourselves or with others to use, copy, distribute, publicly perform, publicly display, print, publish, republish, excerpt (in whole or in part), reformat, translate, modify, revise, and incorporate into other works, content and other works derived from that content, in any form of media or expression, in any manner determined by CAIC, and to license or permit others to do so.
Public Records
The Colorado Open Records Act is applicable to this Privacy Policy pursuant to the Colorado Revised Statutes, Title 24, Article 72, Part 2, which states the following: “It is declared to be the public policy of this state that all public records shall be open for inspection by any person at reasonable times, except as provided in this part 2 or as otherwise specifically provided by law.” A public record is defined here as “all writings made, maintained, or kept by the state, any agency, institution, a nonprofit corporation incorporated pursuant to section 23-5-121 (2), C.R.S., or political subdivision of the state, or that are described in section 29-1-902, C.R.S., and held by any local-government-financed entity for use in the exercise of functions required or authorized by law or administrative rule or involving the receipt or expenditure of public funds.”
If personal information is requested on the website or is volunteered by the user, state and federal law may protect that information. However, all information becomes a public record once it is provided and may be subject to public inspection and copying if not protected by federal or state law.
Cookies
To better serve our users we may use “cookies” to customize your browsing experience with us. Cookies are simple text files stored on your computer by your web browser. They provide a method of distinguishing among visitors to our web site.
Cookies created on your computer by using this web site do not contain personally identifying information and do not compromise your privacy or security. We use the cookie feature only to store a randomly generated identifying tag on your computer. You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer by using any of the widely available methods. Our services are provided in such a way that the use of cookies is not mandatory.
Security
The Information Services division, as developer and manager of the Colorado Secretary of State’s website, has taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its telecommunications and computing infrastructure, including but not limited to authentication, monitoring, and auditing. Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation, and day-to-day practices of the entire operating environment as part of a continuing commitment to risk management.
Disclaimer
The CAIC website contains links to other websites, including websites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations, and private businesses. When you link to another website, you leave our site, which means that this Privacy Policy will no longer apply. When you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of that website.
While CAIC strives to provide the most current and reliable information, avalanche conditions are constantly changing; therefore, portions of information may be incorrect or obsolete.
Neither the CAIC nor any employee of the State of Colorado shall be held liable for any losses resulting from reliance on the accuracy, reliability, or timeliness of such information. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk. Compliance with applicable law remains the responsibility of the user.
Copyright
Some of the materials made available on this website are the intellectual property of CAIC, and are protected by applicable law and may not be reproduced, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of CAIC.
Publications
All publications made available by the Colorado Avalanche Information Center are provided as a public service. By posting to this website, neither the CAIC, nor the author(s) of these publications or articles, are providing legal advice. All publications available on the CAIC website, and any related instructions or documentation, are offered as a public service and no representation or warranty is made concerning the application of the legal or other principles discussed by the authors to any specific fact situation, nor is any prediction made concerning how any particular judge or other official will interpret or apply such principles.
The publications made available have been prepared by a number of authors over a period of years and published at differing times under differing circumstances. The information contained in the publications may be outdated or inaccurate and may be revised from time to time without notice. While the CAIC updates these materials periodically, no representation or warranty is made regarding the accuracy or reliability or concerning the application of the legal or other principles discussed by the author(s) to any specific fact situation. The proper interpretation or application of the principles discussed is a matter for the considered judgment of the user or his/her legal advisor, and the CAIC, the Colorado Department of Natural Resources and it’s’ staff disclaims all liability therefore.
Google PlusFacebookTwitterCloseForecasts
Backcountry Avalanche
Steamboat & Flat Tops
Front Range
Vail & Summit County
Sawatch
Aspen
Gunnison
